

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I would like to be working within a company, offering me new opportunities and challenges. In return, I am a highly motivated individual with a strong work ethic. I always work to my maximum potential, as I enjoy achieving results/targets. I have excellent customer service skills, which are tested on a daily basis in my office. I have sound experience in high pressure settings and bring the additional asset of bilingual communication skills.

SKILLS

- Effective communicator with bilingual skills: Native English/Advanced Spanish.
- Excellent customer service skills often within difficult situations
- Identifying new Business opportunity
- Proficient in developing & growing new market revenue streams
- Computer & Telephone proficient
- Good numerical and analytical skills
- Good ability to work under pressure
- Microsoft Office
- Excel
- Navigating specific Company programs

WORK HISTORY:

Office Manager

Insurance Office, Mojacar

2019 - Present

- Every day running of the office & meeting client's needs
- Proactive sales calls to potential customers educating them on services and products
- Liaising & building with suppliers in order to achieve the best results for the Company
- Up selling to existing clients, generating higher sales
- Maintaining & growing the company profile within the target market
- Developing new business, growing pipeline & closing deals
- Presenting proposals in a professional and timely manner
- Renewals, modifications to renewals in order to reduce customer churn
- Organizing customer accounts and policies, payments and bank transfers
- Resolving of claims, problems with policies and general customer concerns

Best Sun Property Rentals & property management

Self employed

2007 - 2019

- Property maintenance services ensuring rentals are presented at highest standards
- Dealing with tenancy contracts, gaining sign off and negotiating renewals
- Maximizing rental occupancy
- Ensuring properties meet legislative requirements
- Meeting and greeting clients, booking inspections and inventory checks

Adeslas Insurance Mojacar

Insurance Sales

2015 - 2016

- Cold calling to secure new business and meet individual/company targets
- Maintaining existing customer base to reduce churn
- Management of customer accounts, policies and payments
- Providing front of house customer support

Alonso & Haro Solicitors, Vera

Secretary

2006 - 2007

- Organizing legal appointments, paperwork and notary visits
- Delivering bilingual customer care services
- Clerical duties within the legal setting
- Maintaining high level of customer confidentiality

Vivadent Clinica Dental Vera

Dental Assistant

2004 - 2006

- Dental nursing assistant including surgical implants
- Clinical duties including Xrays, equipment preparation and sterilization
- Reception duties, appointment making, liaison and translation for Spanish/English clients

EDUCATION

2002 - 2004

Diploma: Nursing College, Kings Lynn & West Norfolk Nursing College, Kings Lynn

2000 - 2001

Diploma: Art & Design Falmouth College of Arts

1990 - 1994

10 GCSES: 3 x A, 4 x B, 3 x C King Edward VI Upper School, Bury St. Edmunds, Suffolk

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

I have managed a successful integration into a foreign culture, upon moving to Spain in 2004, with my daughter. This was an immensely challenging but satisfying experience and she has embarked on a university degree in Madrid.

I feel that this is now my opportunity to pursue and achieve my personal goals.

I have the drive and determination to take on a new challenge, and believe that the skill set I have would be beneficial to your Company.

I enjoy arts and crafts, I play the flute and enjoy walking. I love the outdoors and being creative.